fl511.com 2010-12-14

# Florida’s 511 Traveler Information System | Privacy Policy

Internet Privacy Policy   
Conditions/Disclaimer

##### Internet Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the Florida's Statewide 511 Web site. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit our Web site unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.

When you visit our Web site, our Web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our Web site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information.

In addition, we gather information regarding the volume and timing of access to our Web site by collecting information on the date, time and Web site pages accessed by visitors to the Web site. We do this so that we can improve the content of our Web site, and this information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected, and individual visitors' personal information is not identified.

If you choose to share personal information with us - sending us a message or filling out an electronic form with personal information - we will use the information only for the purposes you authorized. Some of the information may be saved for a designated period of time to comply with Florida's archiving policies, but we will not disclose the information to third parties or other government agencies, unless required to do so by state or federal law. And if we are required to disclose information about you by law, we will make every effort to notify you of the disclosure in advance.

If you have other questions about our privacy policies, or have ideas about improving our policies, please feel free to [e-mail](mailto:%20fl511@dot.state.fl.us) us or you can reach us by telephone at 850-414-4590.

**Under Florida law, e-mail addresses are public records. If you do not want your e-mail address released in response to a public-records request, do not send electronic mail to this entity. Instead, contact this office by phone or in writing.**

##### Conditions/Disclaimer

My Florida 511 allows its users to register via the My Florida 511 Website and to create a user account. My Florida 511 provides users with access to traveler information (the “information”) through the My Florida 511 Website, Phone System, and Personalized Email, Text Message and Phone Call Alerts. **By visiting the My Florida 511 Website, you agree that you will not use the site for any unlawful activity.** As a consideration of your use of the Service, you agree to: (a) provide true, accurate, and current information and (b) maintain and promptly update account data to keep it true, accurate, current, and complete. 

The Florida Department of Transportation (FDOT) does not guarantee the reliability, accuracy, quality, timeliness, usefulness, adequacy, completeness or suitability of the Information. You should not assume that your use of the MyFlorida 511 service (the “Service”) will be error free or that the Service will operate without interruption. 

You assume all risk arising from your use of the Service, and/or use of the Information retrieved from or sent to you from the Service. FDOT and its licensors shall not be responsible or otherwise liable for any claim, expense, damage, loss, liability, obligation, demand or action, regardless of the nature of the cause of the claim, demand or action, for any direct, indirect, special, incidental, consequential, exemplary, punitive or any other damages arising out of or in connection with the use of or inability to use the Information or the Service, or in reliance on the Information, including any loss of use, lost data, lost business profits, business interruption, personal injury, or any other financial loss, even if FDOT, its contractors, licensors or agents have been informed of the possibility of such loss. 

The mention of another agency or entity in relation to any Information, or to the Service, does not constitute an endorsement, sponsorship or recommendation of that entity or its product or service. 

The use of the Service shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the state of Florida, excluding its conflicts of law rules. Through the use of the Service you expressly agree that the exclusive jurisdiction for any claim or action arising out of or relating to the use of the Site or Services shall be filed only in the state or federal courts located in the state of Florida. 

The Information provided through the Service and all rights to it are owned by the FDOT. Content available through the Service is for individual use only and is not available for re-sale or re-use without the express written consent of FDOT. Upon registration, users of the Service are granted non-exclusive, non-transferable limited license to access and use the Information for personal purposes only (and specifically excluding any commercial use).
